- Add a calendar
- Add dates and important things to the calendar
- Add an option to put deadlines in that calendar feature
- Dynamic UI and UX themes that change automatically according to the month and quarterly arcs (Winter Arc, Spring Arc, Summer Arc, Autumn Arc)
- Specific habit frequency scheduling (e.g., 'twice a week' or specific days for things like Minoxidil) so weekly/monthly scores accurately reflect x/x instead of x/31
